Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory3 Mss.B.B61.inventory03
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents C
  - Conreid, Heinrich (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 26; 1p
  - Conroy, A. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 19; 1p
  - Conseco, M. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 23; 1p
  - Conseil internationale de recherches (Box 17)
    - Det Norske videnskps, 1926 Mar. 16; 1p
      - enc. with Koht, H., 1926 May 2
    - Academia scientiearum, 1926 May 2
  - Constantinovich, Grand Duke Konstantin (Box 17)
    - from Jesup, M.K., 1900 Mar. 9
  - Consumers Union of U.S. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 25
  - Conzemius, E. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 28; 2p
  - Cook, C.J. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1930 July 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 9; 1p
  - Cook, S.J. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Barrows, A.L., 1931 Oct. 28; 1p
  - Cook, Wm. A. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 29
  - Cooley, C.H. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 19; 1p
  - Coolidge, Albert Sprague (Box 17)
    - see Boas open letter, Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Coolidge, W.D. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Cooper, A.H. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 5
  - Cooper, C.B. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 5
  - Cooper, E.H. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 2
  - Cooper, John M. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, Feb. 2, 1931 June 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 17, Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 2; 1p;
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 13; 1p
  - Cooper, Lane (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 2p
  - Cooper, P. (Box 17)
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Cooper, P.A. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p
  - Cooperative Bureau for Teachers (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1940 Sep. 11; 1p
  - Copeland, R.S. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 6; 1p
  - Corben, H.C. (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p
  - Corn Exchange Bank (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1910 May 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 19
    - From Boas, 1911 May 13
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 28; 1p
  - Corn Exchange Bank, Hudson River Branch (also see above) (Box 17)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1908
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1910 Nov. 17
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1914 Feb. 5
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1918 Dec. 12
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1919 Mar. 25
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1919 Apr. 29
    - To Boas For W.Jochelson, 1919 Nov. 6
      See Amer. Relief Administration
      See Eaton, Edward A.
  - Cornelius, C.O. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Cornelius, Laura M. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 7
  - Corner, George (Box 18)
    - To Curtis, C.C., 1908 Nov. 28; 1p
  - Corner [?], L.G. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1907 May 1
  - Cornog, Grace (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1941 July 7; 1p
  - Corona, J.G. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 30
  - Corona Sales Co. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 30
  - Correns, C. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 24; 1p
    - From Stein [?], 1924 July 22
      - Thost, 1924 July 23
  - Correos, Mexico (Box 18)
    - Recipt, 1910 Nov. 7
  - Cortés, A. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 19
  - Corwine, Wm. R. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 19; 1p
    - see Schwab, Gustav H., 1906 Sep. 11
  - Cosentini, F. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 1; 1p
  - Cosmus, T. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 15; 1p
  - Coss, J.J. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 25; 1p
    - To Benedict, R.F., 1932 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Coss, T. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 18; 1p
  - Costa Ferreira, A.A. da (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 7; 3p
  - Costenoble, Herman (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 21
  - Costigan, G.P., Jr. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1918 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 31; 2p
  - Coston, Owen (Box 18)
    - see FB open letter, 1940 June 20
  - Cotheal, Alexander J. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1887 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 29
  - Couch, W.T. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 6; 1p
  - Coudert, F.R., Jr. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Oppenheimer, J.R., 1941 Oct. 13
      - Menzel, Donald H., 1941 Oct. 16
  - Coulet, J. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1913 June 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 June 30
    - To Boas, 1913 June 30
  - Couling, S. (Box 18)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 27
  - Coulter, J.M. (Box 18)
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1918 Mar. 30; 8p
  - Council for Pan American Democracy (Box 18)
    - Activities Mar.-Dec., 1939 Dec.; 4p
      - enc. with Efron, D., 1939 Dec. 6
    - Memo on Luiz Carlos Prestes
      - enc. with McAvoy, C.T., 1939 Oct. 24; 3p
  - Council for Research in the Social Sciences (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1942 May 30; 1p
  - Council of Learned Societies (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 25; 2p
  - Counts, George S. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Efron, D., 1938 Jan. 6; 1p
  - Courlander, Harold (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 2p
  - Coutinho, A.C. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 24; 2p
  - Coutwell, Robt. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
  - Cowan, J.M. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Edel, B.C., 1942 Dec. 30
    - To Edel, B.C., 1943 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Reichard, G.A., 1943 May 3; 1p
  - Coward, T.R. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 1; 1p
  - Cowen, C.A. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 2
  - Cowley, Malcolm (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 30; 1p
    - see Amer. Comm. for World Congress Against War, 1932 May 27
  - Cox (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 24
  - Cox, Philip W.L. (Box 18)
    - see FB open letter, Replies re Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Cox, Richard T. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 19; 1p
  - Coykendall, F. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 9; 1p
  - Cragin, E.F. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 16
  - Cramer, Ehrenfried (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1886 July 9
  - Cramer, G. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 11; 1p
  - Cramer, L.W. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nev. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nev. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 17; 1p
  - Crampton, C. Ward (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 28 and Apr. 7
    - 1908 From Boas, 1908 May 12
    - 1908 From Boss, 1908 Oct. 10
    - 1908 From Boss, 1908 Oct. 16
    - 1908 From Boss, 1908 Dec. 21
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 Jan. 20
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 Apr. 2
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 Apr. 7
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 June 5; 2p
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 June 25
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 Oct. 26
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 Oct. 30
    - 1908 From Boss, 1909 Dec. 24
    - 1908 From Boss, 1931 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 June 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 June 12
    - To Boas, 1909 June 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 4
      - enclosures, 1931 May 22; 1p and4
  - Crampton, H.E. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 4 and Sep. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1916 June 9
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1905 July 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 June 11
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 24
  - Crampton, J.W. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
  - Crane, E.J. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
  - Crane, M.E. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1909 May 3
    - From Boas, 1909 May 5
    - From Boas, 1909 May 7
    - From Boas, 1909 May 8
    - From Boas, 1909 May 18
    - From Boas, 1909 May 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 May 20
    - From Boas, 1909 May 21
    - From Boas, 1909 May 24
    - From Boas, 1909 June 1
    - From Boas, 1909 June 1
    - From Boas, 1909 June 3
    - From Boas, 1909 June 14
    - From Boas, 1909 June 21
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25
    - From Boas, 1909 June 26
    - From Boas, 1909 June 28
    - From Boas, 1909 June 29
    - From Boas, 1909 June 30
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 31
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 May 3
    - From Boas, 1910 May 14
    - From Boas, 1910 May 25
    - From Boas, 1910 May 27
    - From Boas, 1910 May 31
    - From Boas, 1910 June 9
    - From Boas, 1910 June 14
    - From Boas, 1910 June 17
    - From Boas, 1910 June 20
    - From Boas, 1910 June 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 July 26
    - From Boas, 1910 July 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 1
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 13
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 22
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Sep. 26
    - From Boas, 1910 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1909 April 9
    - To Boas, 1909 April 22
    - To Boas, 1909 May 2
    - To Boas, 1909 May 6
    - To Boas, 1909 May 9
    - To Boas, 1909 May 16
    - To Boas, 1909 May 19
    - To Boas, 1909 May 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 31
    - To Boas, 1909 June 2
    - To Boas, 1909 June 4
    - To Boas, 1909 June 5
    - To Boas, 1909 June 5
    - To Boas, 1909 June 6
    - To Boas, 1909 June 19
    - To Boas, 1909 June 26
    - To Boas, 1909 June 27
    - To Boas, 1909 June 29
    - To Boas, 1909 July 3
    - To Boas, 1909 July 14
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 1
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1909 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 May 2
    - To Boas, 1910 May 2
    - To Boas, 1910 May 27
    - To Boas, 1910 May 28
    - To Boas, 1910 June 15
    - To Boas, 1910 June 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 July 6
    - To Boas, 1910 July 27
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Sep. 27, 29
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 28
    - To schwarz, Osias, 1910 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Crane, N. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 6; 2p
  - Crane, R.T. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 27; 1p
  - Crane, T.F. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 2; 2p
  - Cranfaira, C. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 13
  - Cranmer, Dan. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 July 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 12
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Sep. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1941 June 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 2; 1p
  - Cravath, Paul (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 4
  - Crawford, J.W. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 6; 1p
  - Crawford, S.A. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 25; 2p
  - Creel, G. (Box 18)
    - From Irvine, B.F., 1918 Mar. 22; 2p
  - Crees, H.W. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1912 June 18
    - To Boas, 1912 June 22
    - To Boas, 1912 July 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
  - Creese, J. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 27; 1p
  - Creighton, J.E. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p
  - Cremer, T.H. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 24; 2p
  - Creole News Sheet (Box 18)
    - Specimens thru II/23/41, 1940 Oct. 21; 11p
  - Creole (re Teaching) (Box 18)
    - see McConnell, H.O., 1941 Feb. 10
  - Crespi, C. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Crespo y Martinez, Gilberto (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 5; 6p
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 6; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
  - Crist Princting Co. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 5; 1p
  - Crivelli (Box 18)
    - To Holmes, W.H., 1905 Mar. 20
  - Crocker, Wm. H. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p
  - Croll, June (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 30; 2p
  - Crolly, Charles S. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 3
  - Croly, H. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 19; 1p
    - See Trombetti, A., 1926 Mar. 30; 1p
  - Cronau, Rudolf (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 14; 2p
  - Cronau, Mrs. Rudolf (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p
  - Cronberg (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1929 Aug. 12; 2p
  - Cronen (Box 18)
    - List of societies?, 1905 Dec. 31
  - Cronley, Margaret E. (Box 18)
    - To Maynard, J.A., 1920 Aug. 16; 1p
  - Cronyn, George W. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1917 June 12
    - To Boas, 1917 June 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 1
  - Cross, Ephraim -- [or E.] (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 22; 1p
    - see FB open letter-replies, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Cross, Wilbur (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1930 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 19 - 1930 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Crossman, N.H. (Box 18)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 11
  - Crosswaith, Frank R. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 21; 5p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July?
  - Crowell, J.F. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1912 May 13
  - Crowinshield, F. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Croxton, Fred C. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1909 May 8
    - To Boas, 1909 June 3
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 7
  - Croxton, F.E. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31; 2p
  - Crum, F.S. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 26; 1p
  - Crum, Roy W. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 5; 1p
  - Csekanowski, J. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Cuba - Commissioner of Immigration (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Cudrey, E.C. (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 15
  - Culberson, P.T. (Box 18)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p
  - Culin, Stewart (Box 18)
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1901 Nov. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1893 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 19; 1p
  - Cultural Conflict... Italians --, 1935 (Box 18)
  - Cummings, T.F. (Box 18)